<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Dbf name="HERO">
	<SourceFingerprint>KT4EZyfvhEJHXlgOz7EZLW/NLRA=</SourceFingerprint>
	<Column name="ID" type="Int" />
	<Column name="CARD_ID" type="String" />
	<Column name="CARD_BACK_ID" type="Int" />
	<Column name="DESCRIPTION" type="LocString" />
	<Column name="HERODEF_ASSET_PATH" type="AssetPath" />
	<Column name="STORE_DESCRIPTION" type="LocString" />
	<Column name="STORE_DESCRIPTION_PHONE" type="LocString" />
	<Column name="STORE_BANNER_PREFAB" type="AssetPath" />
	<Column name="STORE_BACKGROUND_TEXTURE" type="AssetPath" />
	<Column name="STORE_SORT_ORDER" type="Int" />
	<Column name="PURCHASE_COMPLETE_MSG" type="LocString" />
	<Record>
		<Field column="ID">1</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_ID">HERO_01</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_BACK_ID" />
		<Field column="DESCRIPTION" loc_ID="21107">
			<enUS>This former Warchief of the Horde isn’t bitter about being deposed. Not at all.</enUS>
			<deDE>Dieser ehemalige Kriegshäuptling der Horde mag seinen Thron eingebüßt haben, aber nicht seinen rustikalen Charme.</deDE>
			<esES>Este antiguo Jefe de Guerra de la Horda no está resentido por haber sido destituido. Para nada.</esES>
			<esMX>Este otrora Jefe de guerra de la Horda no guarda ningún resentimiento por su derrocamiento. Para nada.</esMX>
			<frFR>Cet ancien chef de guerre de la Horde n’est pas aigri d’avoir été renversé. Mais alors pas du tout.</frFR>
			<itIT>Il precedente Capoguerra dell'Orda non è per niente dispiaciuto di essere stato deposto. Proprio per niente.</itIT>
			<jaJP>ホードの元戦長。戦長の座を下ろされたことは、特に気にしてない。ああ、これっぽっちもだ。</jaJP>
			<koKR>호드의 대족장 자리를 빼앗겼지만 크게 앙심을 품고 있지는 않습니다. 정말로요.</koKR>
			<plPL>Ten dawny wódz Hordy wcale nie ma żalu o pozbawienie go stanowiska. Nic a nic.</plPL>
			<ptBR>Este antigo Chefe Guerreiro da Horda nem está rancoroso por ter perdido o posto. Imagina.</ptBR>
			<ruRU>Бывший вождь Орды, который не таит зла за то, что его свергли. Ну вот прям ни капельки.</ruRU>
			<thTH>อดีตหัวหน้าเผ่าคนนี้ไม่ได้รู้สึกขมขื่นจากการโดนปลดจากตำแหน่งนะ ไม่ซักนิดเลย</thTH>
			<zhCN>前部落酋长根本不在乎被罢黜。一点儿也不。</zhCN>
			<zhTW>部落的前任大酋長才不會因為被拋棄就傷心呢。絕對不會！</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="HERODEF_ASSET_PATH">Assets/Game/GameObjects/HeroDefs/CollectionHeroDef_01</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION" />
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION_PHONE" />
		<Field column="STORE_BANNER_PREFAB" />
		<Field column="STORE_BACKGROUND_TEXTURE" />
		<Field column="STORE_SORT_ORDER" />
		<Field column="PURCHASE_COMPLETE_MSG" />
	</Record>
	<Record>
		<Field column="ID">2</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_ID">HERO_02</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_BACK_ID" />
		<Field column="DESCRIPTION" loc_ID="21108">
			<enUS>Thrall quit his former job as Warchief to save the world and spend more time with his family.</enUS>
			<deDE>Thrall hat seinen Job als Kriegshäuptling an den Nagel gehängt, um die Welt zu retten – und mehr Zeit mit seiner Familie zu verbringen.</deDE>
			<esES>Thrall renunció a su antiguo trabajo de Jefe de Guerra para salvar el mundo y pasar más tiempo con su familia.</esES>
			<esMX>Thrall renunció a su viejo trabajo como Jefe de guerra para salvar el mundo y pasar más tiempo con su familia.</esMX>
			<frFR>Thrall a quitté son poste de chef de guerre pour sauver le monde et passer plus de temps avec sa famille.</frFR>
			<itIT>Thrall ha rinunciato alla posizione di Capoguerra per salvare il mondo e passare più tempo con la sua famiglia.</itIT>
			<jaJP>戦長として世界を救うべくモーレツに働いていたスロールは、仕事を辞めてからは家族と一緒の時間を大切にしているそうだ。</jaJP>
			<koKR>스랄은 세계 평화를 위해 대족장이라는 책무를 내려두고 가족과 더 시간을 보내기로 마음먹었습니다.</koKR>
			<plPL>Thrall zrezygnował ze stanowiska wodza Hordy, aby uratować świat i spędzać więcej czasu z rodziną.</plPL>
			<ptBR>Thrall abdicou de seu posto de Chefe Guerreiro para salvar o mundo e passar mais tempo com a família.</ptBR>
			<ruRU>Тралл ушел с должности Вождя Орды, чтобы спасти мир и проводить больше времени с семьей.</ruRU>
			<thTH>ธรอลลาออกจากการเป็นหัวหน้าเผ่าเพื่อช่วยโลก และเพื่อให้เขามีเวลาอยู่กับครอบครัวมากขึ้น</thTH>
			<zhCN>为了拯救世界，也为了陪伴家人，萨尔卸下了部落酋长的重担。</zhCN>
			<zhTW>索爾辭掉了大酋長的工作以拯救世界，並且多陪陪家人。</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="HERODEF_ASSET_PATH">Assets/Game/GameObjects/HeroDefs/CollectionHeroDef_02</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION" />
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION_PHONE" />
		<Field column="STORE_BANNER_PREFAB" />
		<Field column="STORE_BACKGROUND_TEXTURE" />
		<Field column="STORE_SORT_ORDER" />
		<Field column="PURCHASE_COMPLETE_MSG" />
	</Record>
	<Record>
		<Field column="ID">3</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_ID">HERO_03</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_BACK_ID" />
		<Field column="DESCRIPTION" loc_ID="21109">
			<enUS>Expert assassin.  Deadly gladiator.  Best knife skills in her cooking class, according to survivors.</enUS>
			<deDE>Profikillerin und Gladiatorenchampion. Glänzte in ihrem Kochkurs durch geschickten Umgang mit Messern_... behaupten zumindest die Überlebenden.</deDE>
			<esES>Asesina experta y gladiadora letal. Mostró una destreza insuperable con los cuchillos en clase de cocina, según comentan los supervivientes.</esES>
			<esMX>Asesina experta. Gladiadora letal. Nadie maneja mejor el cuchillo en su clase de cocina... dicen los sobrevivientes.</esMX>
			<frFR>Tueuse experte. Gladiatrice létale. Meilleur coup de couteau de son cours de cuisine, d’après les survivants.</frFR>
			<itIT>Esperta assassina e micidiale gladiatrice. La migliore con i coltelli del suo corso di cucina, a detta dei sopravvissuti.</itIT>
			<jaJP>一流の暗殺者であり、凄腕の剣闘士。そして、料理教室で一番のナイフの使い手である。（生存者の証言）</jaJP>
			<koKR>노련한 암살자. 잔혹한 검투사. 하지만 발리라와 함께 여행한 자들은 그녀의 뛰어난 요리 솜씨에 더욱 놀란다고 합니다.</koKR>
			<plPL>Doskonała skrytobójczyni. Bezwzględna gladiatorka. A podobno także mistrzyni szatkowania kapusty.</plPL>
			<ptBR>Assassina perita. Gladiadora mortal. Melhores habilidades com faca na aula de culinária (de acordo com os sobreviventes).</ptBR>
			<ruRU>Опытная убийца. Смертоносный гладиатор. А еще видели бы вы, как она работает ножами в кулинарной школе!</ruRU>
			<thTH>มือสังหารผู้เชี่ยวชาญ นักสู้ฝีมือเยี่ยม ผู้ชำนาญการใช้มีดที่สุดในชั้นเรียนทำอาหาร ทั้งหมดนี้คือความเห็นของผู้รอดชีวิต</thTH>
			<zhCN>刺杀专家。致命角斗士。唯一在暴风城中享有崇高威望的血精灵。</zhCN>
			<zhTW>精英殺手，致命鬥士，而且根據生還者所言，她的刀工在料理界也堪稱一絕。</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="HERODEF_ASSET_PATH">Assets/Game/GameObjects/HeroDefs/CollectionHeroDef_03</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION" />
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION_PHONE" />
		<Field column="STORE_BANNER_PREFAB" />
		<Field column="STORE_BACKGROUND_TEXTURE" />
		<Field column="STORE_SORT_ORDER" />
		<Field column="PURCHASE_COMPLETE_MSG" />
	</Record>
	<Record>
		<Field column="ID">4</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_ID">HERO_04</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_BACK_ID" />
		<Field column="DESCRIPTION" loc_ID="21110">
			<enUS>Leader of the Knights of the Silver Hand.  Best-selling author of The Light and How to Swing It.</enUS>
			<deDE>Anführer des Ordens der Silbernen Hand und Autor des Bestsellers „Vom Licht und wie man es schwingt“.</deDE>
			<esES>Líder de los caballeros de la Mano de Plata y autor del popular libro "La Luz y cómo alterarla".</esES>
			<esMX>Líder de los caballeros de la Mano de Plata. Autor del éxito de ventas "La Luz y cómo alterarla".</esMX>
			<frFR>Chef des chevaliers de la Main d’argent. Auteur à succès de « La Lumière et comment l’altérer ».</frFR>
			<itIT>Capo dei Cavalieri della Mano d'Argento. Autore del best seller "Come gestire la Luce".</itIT>
			<jaJP>シルバーハンド騎士団のリーダー。そしてベストセラー「光よ導きたまえ・実践スイング練習法」の著者。</jaJP>
			<koKR>은빛 성기사단의 지도자입니다. '빛과 정의에 관하여'라는 책의 저자이기도 합니다.</koKR>
			<plPL>Dowódca Rycerzy Srebrnej Dłoni. Autor bestsellera „Światłość dla opornych”.</plPL>
			<ptBR>Líder dos Cavaleiros do Punho de Prata. Autor do best-seller "A Luz e como Ativá-la".</ptBR>
			<ruRU>Предводитель Рыцарей Серебряной Длани и автор бессмертного произведения «Раскачаем этот свет».</ruRU>
			<thTH>ผู้นำแห่งอัศวินซิลเวอร์แฮนด์ เจ้าของหนังสือขายดีติดอันดับ "แสงสว่างและการใช้งานอย่างถูกวิธี"</thTH>
			<zhCN>白银之手骑士团的领袖。年度畅销读物《圣光之力》的作者。</zhCN>
			<zhTW>白銀之手騎士團的首領。讓他出名的不只是聖光，還有手中的大錘。</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="HERODEF_ASSET_PATH">Assets/Game/GameObjects/HeroDefs/CollectionHeroDef_04</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION" />
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION_PHONE" />
		<Field column="STORE_BANNER_PREFAB" />
		<Field column="STORE_BACKGROUND_TEXTURE" />
		<Field column="STORE_SORT_ORDER" />
		<Field column="PURCHASE_COMPLETE_MSG" />
	</Record>
	<Record>
		<Field column="ID">5</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_ID">HERO_05</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_BACK_ID" />
		<Field column="DESCRIPTION" loc_ID="21111">
			<enUS>He only feels at home in the wilderness with his beasts.  Super secret:  Misha is his favorite.</enUS>
			<deDE>Wirklich wohl fühlt er sich nur in der Wildnis mit seinen Tieren. Pssst: Misha mag er am liebsten.</deDE>
			<esES>Solo se siente cómodo en plena naturaleza con sus bestias. Un secreto: Misha es su favorita.</esES>
			<esMX>Solo se siente en casa en la naturaleza rodeado de sus bestias. No le digas a nadie, pero Misha es su favorita.</esMX>
			<frFR>Il ne se sent chez lui que dans la nature avec ses bêtes. Super secret : c’est Misha qu’il préfère.</frFR>
			<itIT>Si sente davvero a casa solo nelle terre selvagge, insieme alle sue bestie. Segreto: Misha è la sua preferita!</itIT>
			<jaJP>彼の「憩いの我が家」は人里離れた荒野。そして\n猛獣たちが彼の友だ。（マル秘情報: 彼の一番の\nお気に入りはミーシャ）</jaJP>
			<koKR>야수들과 함께 야생에 있는 걸 가장 좋아합니다. 비밀 하나 알려드릴까요? 그중 미샤를 제일로 아낀다고 하네요.</koKR>
			<plPL>Najlepiej czuje się w dziczy, w towarzystwie swoich bestii. Zdradzę sekret: jego ulubieńcem jest Misza.</plPL>
			<ptBR>Ele só se sente em casa na mata, com suas feras. (Segredo suuuper secreto: Misha é o favorito dele).</ptBR>
			<ruRU>Он чувствует себя как дома только в чаще лесов в окружении своих зверей. Миша, кстати, его любимица. Только никому ни слова!</ruRU>
			<thTH>เขาจะรู้สึกอุ่นใจก็ต่อเมื่อได้อยู่ในป่ากับเหล่าสัตว์ของเขาเท่านั้น ความลับสุดยอด: มิชาคือตัวโปรดของเขา</thTH>
			<zhCN>在浪迹天涯的岁月里，只有野兽的陪伴才能够给他家的温暖。而巨熊米莎则是他的最爱。</zhCN>
			<zhTW>他只有和動物夥伴在野外的時候，才有回家的感覺。噓，他對米莎比較偏心！</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="HERODEF_ASSET_PATH">Assets/Game/GameObjects/HeroDefs/CollectionHeroDef_05</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION" />
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION_PHONE" />
		<Field column="STORE_BANNER_PREFAB" />
		<Field column="STORE_BACKGROUND_TEXTURE" />
		<Field column="STORE_SORT_ORDER" />
		<Field column="PURCHASE_COMPLETE_MSG" />
	</Record>
	<Record>
		<Field column="ID">6</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_ID">HERO_06</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_BACK_ID" />
		<Field column="DESCRIPTION" loc_ID="21112">
			<enUS>The lord of the night elves is a wise and noble leader.  Yes, those antlers are real.</enUS>
			<deDE>Der Herr der Nachtelfen ist ein weiser und edelmütiger Anführer. Und ja, das Geweih ist echt.</deDE>
			<esES>El señor de los elfos de la noche es un líder sabio y noble, y sí, esa cornamenta es de verdad.</esES>
			<esMX>El señor de los elfos de la noche es un líder sabio y noble. Y sí, esos cuernos son de verdad.</esMX>
			<frFR>Le seigneur des elfes de la nuit est un chef sage et noble. Et oui, ses bois sont vrais.</frFR>
			<itIT>Il signore degli Elfi della Notte è un saggio e nobile condottiero. E sì, quelle corna sono vere.</itIT>
			<jaJP>ナイトエルフの長であり、賢明にして気高き\n指導者だ。ああ、あの枝角は本物だよ。</jaJP>
			<koKR>나이트 엘프의 지혜롭고 고결한 지도자입니다. 네, 뿔 맞습니다. 장식이 아니라고요.</koKR>
			<plPL>Władca nocnych elfów to mądry i szlachetny przywódca. I tak, to poroże jest prawdziwe.</plPL>
			<ptBR>O senhor dos elfos noturnos é um líder sábio e nobre. E aquilo não são "chifres", são "galhadas".</ptBR>
			<ruRU>Владыка ночных эльфов — мудрый и благородный правитель. И хватит уже шуточек про его рога.</ruRU>
			<thTH>ราชาแห่งไนท์เอลฟ์เป็นผู้นำที่ชาญฉลาดและมีคุณธรรม ใช่แล้ว เขากวางพวกนั้นเป็นของจริง</thTH>
			<zhCN>暗夜精灵的领袖，睿智而高贵的大德鲁伊。没错，那些鹿角是真货。</zhCN>
			<zhTW>夜精靈的首領是真正高尚又充滿智慧的領導者，而且那對鹿角也是真的。</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="HERODEF_ASSET_PATH">Assets/Game/GameObjects/HeroDefs/CollectionHeroDef_06</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION" />
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION_PHONE" />
		<Field column="STORE_BANNER_PREFAB" />
		<Field column="STORE_BACKGROUND_TEXTURE" />
		<Field column="STORE_SORT_ORDER" />
		<Field column="PURCHASE_COMPLETE_MSG" />
	</Record>
	<Record>
		<Field column="ID">7</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_ID">HERO_07</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_BACK_ID" />
		<Field column="DESCRIPTION" loc_ID="21113">
			<enUS>Talented, persuasive and hard-working.  Too bad he wants to feed your soul to demons.</enUS>
			<deDE>Talentiert, zielorientiert und sehr überzeugend. Wenn Ihr Euch mit ihm einlasst, solltet Ihr Eure Seele gut im Auge behalten.</deDE>
			<esES>Con talento, persuasivo y trabajador. Es una pena que quiera alimentar a los demonios con tu alma.</esES>
			<esMX>Talentoso, persuasivo, trabajador... Lástima que quiera alimentar a los demonios con tu alma.</esMX>
			<frFR>Talentueux, persuasif et travailleur. Dommage qu’il veuille donner votre âme en pâture aux démons.</frFR>
			<itIT>Talentuoso, persuasivo e diligente. Peccato che voglia dare la tua anima in pasto ai demoni.</itIT>
			<jaJP>才能に溢れ、弁が立ち、しかも努力家。あんたの魂を悪魔に捧げようとするのはご愛嬌。</jaJP>
			<koKR>재능이 넘치고 언변이 뛰어난데다 부지런합니다. 당신의 영혼을 악마에게 먹이려고 하는 게 문제죠.</koKR>
			<plPL>Utalentowany, elokwentny i pracowity. Szkoda, że chce nakarmić demony twoją duszą.</plPL>
			<ptBR>Talentoso, persuasivo e dedicado. Pena que ele quer dar sua alma de comer pros demônios.</ptBR>
			<ruRU>Талантливый, упорный и трудолюбивый. Ни перед чем не остановится, чтобы скормить вашу душу демонам.</ruRU>
			<thTH>มีพรสวรรค์ สามารถโน้มน้าวใจได้ และทำงานหนัก น่าเสียดายที่เขาต้องการนำวิญญาณของคุณไปเป็นอาหารของปีศาจ</thTH>
			<zhCN>天赋异禀、能言善道、刻苦努力的术士。可惜他一心想做的事情就是把你的灵魂送给恶魔。</zhCN>
			<zhTW>天資聰穎、辯才無礙、又奮發向上，可惜他的目標是把你的靈魂獻給惡魔。</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="HERODEF_ASSET_PATH">Assets/Game/GameObjects/HeroDefs/CollectionHeroDef_07</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION" />
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION_PHONE" />
		<Field column="STORE_BANNER_PREFAB" />
		<Field column="STORE_BACKGROUND_TEXTURE" />
		<Field column="STORE_SORT_ORDER" />
		<Field column="PURCHASE_COMPLETE_MSG" />
	</Record>
	<Record>
		<Field column="ID">8</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_ID">HERO_08</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_BACK_ID" />
		<Field column="DESCRIPTION" loc_ID="21114">
			<enUS>The Kirin Tor’s leader is a powerful sorceress.  She used to be a lot nicer before the Theramore thing.</enUS>
			<deDE>Mächtige Magierin und Anführerin der Kirin Tor. Sie hat seit dem „Theramore-Vorfall“ leichte Aggressionsprobleme.</deDE>
			<esES>La líder del Kirin Tor es una poderosa hechicera, aunque solía ser mucho más simpática antes de todo ese asunto de Theramore.</esES>
			<esMX>La líder del Kirin Tor es una hechicera poderosa. Era mucho más amable antes del incidente de Theramore.</esMX>
			<frFR>La dirigeante du Kirin Tor est une puissante ensorceleuse. Elle était bien plus sympa avant cette histoire de Theramore.</frFR>
			<itIT>Il capo del Kirin Tor è una potente Maga. Era indubbiamente più amichevole prima della distruzione di Theramore.</itIT>
			<jaJP>キリン・トアの指導者で強力な魔術師だ。人当たりもよかったんだ、あのセラモアの件が起こる前までは。</jaJP>
			<koKR>강력한 여마법사인 제이나는 키린 토의 수장입니다. 테라모어에서 일어난 참사만 아니었어도 훨씬 상냥했을텐데 말이죠.</koKR>
			<plPL>Przywódczyni Kirin Toru to potężna czarodziejka. Ale była znacznie cieplejsza przed wydarzeniami w Theramore.</plPL>
			<ptBR>A líder do Kirin Tor é uma feiticeira poderosa. Ela era mais legal antes daquele lance em Theramore.</ptBR>
			<ruRU>Предводительница Кирин-Тора, бесспорно, могучая чародейка. Но история с Терамором основательно подпортила ее характер.</ruRU>
			<thTH>ผู้นำของคิรินทอร์เป็นจอมเวทที่ทรงพลัง เธอเคยนิสัยดีกว่านี้เยอะ ก่อนที่จะเกิดเรื่องขึ้นที่เธอรามอร์</thTH>
			<zhCN>肯瑞托的领袖，强大的法师。曾经优柔温良而善解人意的她，被骇人听闻的塞拉摩事件彻底改变了。</zhCN>
			<zhTW>祈倫托首領是位強大的法師，她在塞拉摩那些事發生之前，是個相當和善的人。</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="HERODEF_ASSET_PATH">Assets/Game/GameObjects/HeroDefs/CollectionHeroDef_08</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION" />
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION_PHONE" />
		<Field column="STORE_BANNER_PREFAB" />
		<Field column="STORE_BACKGROUND_TEXTURE" />
		<Field column="STORE_SORT_ORDER" />
		<Field column="PURCHASE_COMPLETE_MSG" />
	</Record>
	<Record>
		<Field column="ID">9</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_ID">HERO_09</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_BACK_ID" />
		<Field column="DESCRIPTION" loc_ID="21115">
			<enUS>The future King of Stormwind is a kind, gentle soul.  Except when he’s in Shadowform.</enUS>
			<deDE>Der zukünftige König Sturmwinds ist ein guter Junge ... in Schattengestalt manchmal aber sehr unartig.</deDE>
			<esES>El futuro Rey de Ventormenta es un alma noble y gentil. Excepto cuando está en Forma de las Sombras.</esES>
			<esMX>El futuro rey de Ventormenta es un alma amable y gentil. Excepto cuando está en Forma de las sombras.</esMX>
			<frFR>Le futur roi de Hurlevent est une âme douce et bonne. Sauf quand il est en forme d’Ombre.</frFR>
			<itIT>Il futuro Re di Roccavento è una persona dall'animo gentile. Tranne quando è in Forma d'Ombra.</itIT>
			<jaJP>ストームウィンドの未来の王は、優しく親切な青年だ。※ただし「影なる姿」ではない時に限る。</jaJP>
			<koKR>훗날에 스톰윈드의 왕좌를 계승할 안두인은 너그러운 마음씨를 가지고 있습니다. 어둠의 형상을 사용하기 전까지는요.</koKR>
			<plPL>Przyszły król Wichrogrodu to miła i serdeczna osoba. No chyba że jest w Postaci Cienia.</plPL>
			<ptBR>O futuro rei de Ventobravo é uma alma gentil e bondosa. Menos quando está em Forma de Sombra.</ptBR>
			<ruRU>Будущий король Штормграда добр и мил... пока не примет облик Тьмы.</ruRU>
			<thTH>ว่าที่ราชาแห่งสตอร์มวินด์เป็นคนที่มีจิตใจอ่อนโยนและสุภาพ ยกเว้นเฉพาะตอนที่เขาอยู่ในร่างมืดนะ</thTH>
			<zhCN>暴风城未来的国王有一颗善良而谦和的灵魂，除了他进入暗影形态的时候。</zhCN>
			<zhTW>暴風城未來的國王有著善良和溫柔的靈魂，但在暗影型態的時候除外。</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="HERODEF_ASSET_PATH">Assets/Game/GameObjects/HeroDefs/CollectionHeroDef_09</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION" />
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION_PHONE" />
		<Field column="STORE_BANNER_PREFAB" />
		<Field column="STORE_BACKGROUND_TEXTURE" />
		<Field column="STORE_SORT_ORDER" />
		<Field column="PURCHASE_COMPLETE_MSG" />
	</Record>
	<Record>
		<Field column="ID">10</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_ID">HERO_01a</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_BACK_ID">26</Field>
		<Field column="DESCRIPTION" loc_ID="21116">
			<enUS>Lord of Ironforge. King of Khaz Modan. Grand Explorer. Moira’s Dad. Most Huggable Leader.</enUS>
			<deDE>Herr von Eisenschmiede, König von Khaz Modan, berühmter Entdecker, Moiras Papa und ein bär(t)iger Anführer.</deDE>
			<esES>Señor de Forjaz, rey de Khaz Modan, gran explorador, padre de Moira y el líder más entrañable de todos.</esES>
			<esMX>Señor de Forjaz. Rey de Khaz Modan. Explorador supremo. Padre de Moira. Líder más adorable.</esMX>
			<frFR>Seigneur de Forgefer. Roi de Khaz’Modan. Grand explorateur. Père de Moira. Chef le plus affectueux.</frFR>
			<itIT>Signore di Forgiardente, Re di Khaz Modan, grande esploratore, padre di Moira. L'eroe più abbracciabile di tutti!</itIT>
			<jaJP>アイアンフォージ族の長。カズモダンの王。偉大なる探検家。モイラの父親。「抱きしめたくなる指導者」No.1（当社調べ）。</jaJP>
			<koKR>아이언포지의 국왕. 카즈 모단의 지배자. 위대한 탐험가. 모이라의 아버지. 그리고 껴안아줄 때 가장 푹신푹신한 지도자 1위에 등극한 인물입니다.</koKR>
			<plPL>Władca Żelaznej Kuźni. Król Khaz Modan. Wielki odkrywca. Ojciec Moiry. Najbardziej przytulaśny przywódca.</plPL>
			<ptBR>Senhor de Altaforja. Rei de Khaz Modan. Grande explorador. Papai de Moira. Líder mais fofolento.</ptBR>
			<ruRU>Правитель Стальгорна. Король Каз Модана. Великий исследователь. Папаша Мойры. Обожаемый предводитель.</ruRU>
			<thTH>ลอร์ดแห่งไอรอนฟอร์จ ราชาแห่งคาซโมดาน ยอดนักสำรวจ พ่อของมอยร่า ผู้นำที่น่ากอดที่สุด</thTH>
			<zhCN>铁炉堡的主人。卡兹莫丹的国王。伟大的探索者。茉艾拉的父亲。最平易近人的领袖。</zhCN>
			<zhTW>鐵爐堡國王、卡茲莫丹之王、偉大的探險家、茉艾拉的老爸、還有讓人最想要抱緊處理的國王。</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="HERODEF_ASSET_PATH">Assets/Game/GameObjects/HeroDefs/CollectionHeroDef_01a</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION" loc_ID="21117">
			<enUS>King Magni comes with an animated portrait, new visual effects, emotes and adds a new card back to your collection!\n\nMagni uses your existing warrior cards and the standard warrior hero power.</enUS>
			<deDE>König Magni bietet ein animiertes Porträt, angepasste visuelle Effekte, neue Emotes und einen brandneuen Kartenrücken!\nMagni kämpft mit Kriegerkarten und der Standard-Heldenfähigkeit des Kriegers.</deDE>
			<esES>El rey Magni viene con un retrato animado, nuevos efectos visuales y frases, ¡y añade un nuevo dorso de carta a tu colección!\n\nMagni utiliza tus cartas de guerrero y el poder de héroe de guerrero normal.</esES>
			<esMX>El Rey Magni viene con un retrato animado, nuevos efectos visuales y emociones. ¡Además agregará un dorso de carta a tu colección!\n\nMagni usa las cartas de guerrero que ya tienes y el poder de héroe estándar de esa clase.</esMX>
			<frFR>Le roi Magni comprend un portrait animé, de nouveaux effets visuels, des emotes et un nouveau dos de carte pour votre collection !\n\nMagni utilise les cartes guerrier déjà en votre possession et le pouvoir héroïque standard du guerrier.</frFR>
			<itIT>Re Magni si presenta con un ritratto animato, nuovi effetti visivi ed emote, e aggiunge un nuovo dorso alla tua collezione!\n\nMagni usa il Potere Eroe e le carte in tuo possesso del Guerriero.</itIT>
			<jaJP>マグニ王カードには：動く肖像画、新たなエフェクト効果、\nマグニならではの表現セリフ、そして新たなカード裏面\nデザインがついてきます！\n\nマグニは既存のウォリアー用のカードと、通常のウォリアーのヒーローパワーを使用します。</jaJP>
			<koKR>국왕 마그니 세트에는 움직이는 초상화, 새로운 시각 효과, 감정 표현, 그리고 카드 뒷면이 포함되어 있습니다!\n\n마그니는 내가 보유한 전사 카드와 전사의 기본 영웅 능력을 사용합니다.</koKR>
			<plPL>Król Magni dostępny jest wraz z animowanym portretem, nowymi efektami wizualnymi, emotkami oraz nowym rewersem kart.\n\nMagni wykorzystuje istniejące karty wojownika oraz jego standardową moc specjalną.</plPL>
			<ptBR>O Rei Magni vem com um retrato animado, novos efeitos visuais, expressões e adiciona um novo verso de card à sua coleção!\n\nMagni usa seus cards de guerreiro existentes e o poder heroico de guerreiro padrão.</ptBR>
			<ruRU>К этому герою прилагается анимированный портрет, новые графические эффекты, эмоции и новая рубашка для карт в вашей коллекции!\n\nКороль Магни может использовать ваши карты воина и стандартную силу героя.</ruRU>
			<thTH>ราชาแม็กนิมาพร้อมกับภาพประจำตัวขยับได้ รวมถึงวิชวลเอฟเฟกต์และการแสดงความรู้สึกแบบใหม่ และยังเพิ่มหลังการ์ดลายใหม่ให้คอลเลกชันของคุณด้วย!\n\nแม็กนิจะใช้การ์ดวอริเออร์ของคุณ รวมถึงพลังฮีโร่มาตรฐานของวอริเออร์</thTH>
			<zhCN>购买矮人国王麦格尼即可获得新的英雄头像、全新动画效果、表情以及一款新的卡牌背面图案！\n\n麦格尼将使用你现有的战士卡牌和英雄技能。</zhCN>
			<zhTW>麥格尼國王擁有獨特的動態頭像，新的視覺效果和表情語音，並且還會增加一張全新的卡背到你的收藏中！\n\n麥格尼可以沿用你擁有的戰士卡牌和英雄能力。</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION_PHONE" loc_ID="22453">
			<enUS>Includes a new portrait, more visual effects &amp; emotes, and a card back!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Uses existing Warrior cards and hero power.&lt;/color&gt;</enUS>
			<deDE>Umfasst ein neues Porträt, neue visuelle Effekte &amp; Emotes und einen Kartenrücken!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Verwendet schon bestehende Kriegerkarten und die gleiche Heldenfähigkeit.&lt;/color&gt;</deDE>
			<esES>¡Incluye un nuevo retrato, más efectos visuales y frases, y un dorso de carta!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Utiliza las cartas y el poder de héroe del guerrero.&lt;/color&gt;</esES>
			<esMX>Incluye un retrato nuevo, más efectos visuales y emociones, ¡y un dorso de carta!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Usa el poder de héroe y las cartas de Guerrero existentes.&lt;/color&gt;</esMX>
			<frFR>Comprend de nouveaux effets visuels, emotes, un portrait et un dos de carte !\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Utilise les cartes et le pouvoir héroïque de la classe guerrier.&lt;/color&gt;</frFR>
			<itIT>Include un nuovo ritratto, effetti visivi ed emote, e un dorso per le carte!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Usa il Potere Eroe e le carte della classe Guerriero.&lt;/color&gt;</itIT>
			<jaJP>新しい肖像画と視覚効果、専用の感情表現セリフと、新しいカード裏面デザインがついてくる！\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;既存のウォリアー用のカードとヒーローパワーを使用。&lt;/color&gt;</jaJP>
			<koKR>새로운 초상화, 시각 효과, 감정 표현, 그리고 카드 뒷면이 포함되어 있습니다!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;내가 보유한 전사 카드와 기본 영웅 능력을 사용합니다.&lt;/color&gt;</koKR>
			<plPL>Zawiera nowy portret, więcej efektów wizualnych\ni emotek oraz nowy rewers!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Wykorzystuje istniejące karty oraz moc specjalną wojownika.&lt;/color&gt;</plPL>
			<ptBR>Inclui um novo retrato, mais expressões e efeitos visuais e um verso de card!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Usa cards de Guerreiro e poder heroico.&lt;/color&gt;</ptBR>
			<ruRU>Включает в себя новый портрет, расширенные графические эффекты и эмоции, а также рубашку для карт. \n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Использует имеющиеся карты воина, а также стандартную силу героя. &lt;/color&gt;</ruRU>
			<thTH>มาพร้อมกับภาพประจำตัวใหม่ เพิ่มวิชวลเอฟเฟกต์และการแสดงความรู้สึก รวมถึงหลังการ์ด!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;ใช้การ์ดและพลังฮีโร่ของวอริเออร์ที่มีอยู่เดิม&lt;/color&gt;</thTH>
			<zhCN>购买即可获得新的英雄头像、全新动画效果、表情以及一款新的卡牌背面图案！\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;该英雄将使用你现有的战士卡牌和英雄技能。&lt;/color&gt;</zhCN>
			<zhTW>包括一套新的頭像，視覺效果，表情語音和卡背！\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;沿用既有的戰士卡牌和英雄能力。&lt;/color&gt;</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_BANNER_PREFAB" />
		<Field column="STORE_BACKGROUND_TEXTURE" />
		<Field column="STORE_SORT_ORDER">1</Field>
		<Field column="PURCHASE_COMPLETE_MSG" />
	</Record>
	<Record>
		<Field column="ID">11</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_ID">HERO_05a</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_BACK_ID">25</Field>
		<Field column="DESCRIPTION" loc_ID="21118">
			<enUS>The high elf Ranger Captain is a peerless archer. Ask any of the orcs she used for target practice.</enUS>
			<deDE>Diese Elfenwaldläuferin ist eine beispiellose Bogenschützin. Fragt nur mal die Orcs, die für sie als Ziele herhalten mussten.</deDE>
			<esES>La Capitán Forestal de los elfos nobles es una arquera sin par. Pregúntaselo a cualquiera de los orcos que utilizó para practicar.</esES>
			<esMX>La Capitana forestal de los elfos nobles es una arquera sin igual. Si no me crees, pregúntale a cualquiera de los orcos que ha usado para practicar.</esMX>
			<frFR>Le capitaine des Forestiers haut-elfe est une archère hors pair. Vous n’avez qu’à demander aux orcs qui lui ont servi de cible d’entraînement.</frFR>
			<itIT>L'Alta Elfa e Capitano dei Guardaboschi è un'eccellente arciera. Chiedi conferma agli Orchi su cui fa pratica.</itIT>
			<jaJP>ハイエルフのレンジャー隊長は天下無双の弓の\n使い手だ。嘘だと思うなら、訓練用の的にされた\nオークたちに聞いてみな。</jaJP>
			<koKR>하이 엘프의 순찰대장인 알레리아는 뛰어난 궁수입니다. 그녀의 표적이 된 오크들은 이를 너무나도 잘 알죠.</koKR>
			<plPL>Kapitan Tropicieli wysokich elfów to wyśmienita łuczniczka. Zapytaj dowolnego orka, na którym ćwiczyła.</plPL>
			<ptBR>A capitã-patrulheira élfica é uma arqueira sem igual. Pergunte a um dos orcs que ela usou de alvo no treino.</ptBR>
			<ruRU>Капитан следопытов высших эльфов просто обязана быть искусной лучницей. Орки, которые послужили ей тренировочными мишенями, могут подтвердить.</ruRU>
			<thTH>หัวหน้าหน่วยเรนเจอร์แห่งไฮเอลฟ์คือนักธนูฝีมือดีที่สุด ลองถามพวกออร์คที่เธอใช้เป็นเป้าฝึกยิงดูก็ได้</thTH>
			<zhCN>高等精灵游侠将军，独步天下的神射手。死在她箭下的兽人士兵数不胜数。</zhCN>
			<zhTW>這位高等精靈遊俠隊長是舉世無雙的神射手，不信的話，問問被她拿來當靶的獸人就知道了。</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="HERODEF_ASSET_PATH">Assets/Game/GameObjects/HeroDefs/CollectionHeroDef_05a</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION" loc_ID="21119">
			<enUS>Ranger Alleria comes with an animated portrait, new visual effects, emotes and adds a new card back to your collection! \n\nAlleria uses your existing hunter cards and the standard hunter hero power.</enUS>
			<deDE>Die Waldläuferin Alleria bietet ein animiertes Porträt, angepasste visuelle Effekte, neue Emotes und einen brandneuen Kartenrücken!\nAlleria kämpft mit Jägerkarten und der Standard-Heldenfähigkeit des Jägers.</deDE>
			<esES>La forestal Alleria viene con un retrato animado, nuevos efectos visuales y frases, ¡y añade un nuevo dorso de carta a tu colección!\n\nAlleria utiliza tus cartas de cazador y el poder de héroe de cazador normal.</esES>
			<esMX>La Capitana forestal Alleria viene con un retrato animado, nuevos efectos visuales y emociones. ¡Además agregará un dorso de carta a tu colección!\n\nAlleria usa las cartas de cazador que ya tienes y el poder de héroe estándar de esa clase.</esMX>
			<frFR>Le capitaine des Forestiers Alleria comprend un portrait animé, de nouveaux effets visuels, des emotes et un nouveau dos de carte pour votre collection !\n\nAlleria utilise les cartes chasseur déjà en votre possession et le pouvoir héroïque standard du chasseur.</frFR>
			<itIT>La Guardaboschi Alleria si presenta con un ritratto animato, nuovi effetti visivi ed emote, e aggiunge un nuovo dorso alla tua collezione!\n\nAlleria usa il Potere Eroe e le carte in tuo possesso del Cacciatore.</itIT>
			<jaJP>レンジャーのアレリアには：動く肖像画、新たなエフェクト\n効果、アレリアならではの表現セリフ、そして新たなカード\n裏面デザインがついてきます！\n\nアレリアは既存のハンター用のカードと、通常のハンターのヒーローパワーを使用します。</jaJP>
			<koKR>순찰대장 알레리아 세트에는 움직이는 초상화, 새로운 시각 효과, 감정 표현, 그리고 카드 뒷면이 포함되어 있습니다!\n\n알레리아는 내가 보유한 사냥꾼 카드와 사냥꾼의 기본 영웅 능력을 사용합니다.</koKR>
			<plPL>Tropicielka Alleria dostępna jest wraz z animowanym portretem, nowymi efektami wizualnymi, emotkami oraz nowym rewersem kart.\n\nAlleria wykorzystuje istniejące karty łowcy oraz jego standardową moc specjalną.</plPL>
			<ptBR>A Patrulheira Alleria vem com um retrato animado, novos efeitos visuais, expressões e adiciona um novo verso de card à sua coleção!\n\nAlleria usa seus cards de caçador existentes e o poder heroico de caçador padrão.</ptBR>
			<ruRU>К этому герою прилагается анимированный портрет, новые графические эффекты, эмоции и новая рубашка для карт в вашей коллекции!\n\nАллерия может использовать ваши карты охотника и стандартную силу героя.</ruRU>
			<thTH>เรนเจอร์อัลลีเรียมาพร้อมกับภาพประจำตัวขยับได้ รวมถึงวิชวลเอฟเฟกต์และการแสดงความรู้สึกแบบใหม่ และยังเพิ่มหลังการ์ดลายใหม่ให้คอลเลกชันของคุณด้วย! \n\nอัลลีเรียจะใช้การ์ดฮันเตอร์ของคุณ รวมถึงพลังฮีโร่มาตรฐานของฮันเตอร์</thTH>
			<zhCN>购买游侠奥蕾莉亚即可获得新的英雄头像、全新动画效果、表情以及一款新的卡牌背面图案！\n\n奥蕾莉亚将使用你现有的猎人卡牌和英雄技能。</zhCN>
			<zhTW>遊俠艾蘭里亞擁有獨特的動態頭像，新的視覺效果和表情語音，並且還會增加一張全新的卡背到你的收藏！\n\n艾蘭里亞可以沿用你擁有的獵人卡牌和英雄能力。</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION_PHONE" loc_ID="22454">
			<enUS>Includes a new portrait, more visual effects &amp; emotes, and a card back!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Uses existing Hunter cards and hero power.&lt;/color&gt;</enUS>
			<deDE>Umfasst ein neues Porträt, neue visuelle Effekte &amp; Emotes und einen Kartenrücken!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Verwendet schon bestehende Jägerkarten und die gleiche Heldenfähigkeit.&lt;/color&gt;</deDE>
			<esES>¡Incluye un nuevo retrato, más efectos visuales y frases, y un dorso de carta!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Utiliza las cartas y el poder de héroe del cazador.&lt;/color&gt;</esES>
			<esMX>Incluye un retrato nuevo, más efectos visuales y emociones, ¡y un dorso de carta!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Usa el poder de héroe y las cartas de Cazador existentes.&lt;/color&gt;</esMX>
			<frFR>Comprend de nouveaux effets visuels, emotes, un portrait et un dos de carte !\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Utilise les cartes et le pouvoir héroïque de la classe chasseur.&lt;/color&gt;</frFR>
			<itIT>Include un nuovo ritratto, effetti visivi ed emote, e un dorso per le carte!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Usa il Potere Eroe e le carte della classe Cacciatore.&lt;/color&gt;</itIT>
			<jaJP>新しい肖像画と視覚効果、専用の感情表現セリフと、新しいカード裏面デザインがついてくる！\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;既存のハンター用のカードとヒーローパワーを使用。&lt;/color&gt;</jaJP>
			<koKR>새로운 초상화, 시각 효과, 감정 표현, 그리고 카드 뒷면이 포함되어 있습니다!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;내가 보유한 사냥꾼 카드와 기본 영웅 능력을 사용합니다.&lt;/color&gt;</koKR>
			<plPL>Zawiera nowy portret, więcej efektów wizualnych\ni emotek, a także nowy rewers!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Wykorzystuje istniejące karty oraz moc specjalną łowcy.&lt;/color&gt;</plPL>
			<ptBR>Inclui um novo retrato, mais expressões e efeitos visuais e um verso de card!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Usa cards de Caçador e poder heroico.&lt;/color&gt;</ptBR>
			<ruRU>Включает в себя новый портрет, расширенные графические эффекты и эмоции, а также рубашку для карт. \n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Использует имеющиеся карты  охотника, а также стандартную силу героя. &lt;/color&gt;</ruRU>
			<thTH>มาพร้อมกับภาพประจำตัวใหม่ เพิ่มวิชวลเอฟเฟกต์และการแสดงความรู้สึก รวมถึงหลังการ์ด!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;ใช้การ์ดและพลังฮีโร่ของฮันเตอร์ที่มีอยู่เดิม&lt;/color&gt;</thTH>
			<zhCN>购买即可获得新的英雄头像、全新动画效果、表情以及一款新的卡牌背面图案！\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;该英雄将使用你现有的猎人卡牌和英雄技能。&lt;/color&gt;</zhCN>
			<zhTW>包括一套新的頭像，視覺效果，表情語音和卡背！\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;沿用既有的獵人卡牌和英雄能力。&lt;/color&gt;</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_BANNER_PREFAB" />
		<Field column="STORE_BACKGROUND_TEXTURE" />
		<Field column="STORE_SORT_ORDER">2</Field>
		<Field column="PURCHASE_COMPLETE_MSG" />
	</Record>
	<Record>
		<Field column="ID">12</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_ID">HERO_08a</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_BACK_ID">27</Field>
		<Field column="DESCRIPTION" loc_ID="21120">
			<enUS>The Guardian of Tirisfal is a force for good.  Demonic possession is a manageable condition.</enUS>
			<deDE>Der Wächter von Tirisfal ist ein Kämpfer für das Gute! Dass er von einem gefallenen Titanen besessen ist, beeinflusst ihn kein bisschen.</deDE>
			<esES>El guardián de Tirisfal es una fuerza del bien. La posesión demoníaca es una condición manejable.</esES>
			<esMX>El Guardián de Tirisfal es una fuerza del bien. La posesión demoníaca es un trastorno completamente controlable.</esMX>
			<frFR>Le gardien de Tirisfal est une force agissant pour le bien. La possession démoniaque, il gère.</frFR>
			<itIT>Il Guardiano di Tirisfal è una forza del bene. La possessione demoniaca è una condizione assolutamente gestibile.</itIT>
			<jaJP>ティリスファルのガーディアンは正義の守護者だ。\n少々悪魔に支配されていましたが、実用には問題\nありません。</jaJP>
			<koKR>티리스팔의 수호자인 메디브는 선한 마음씨를 가지고 있습니다. 가끔 악마에 지배당하긴 했지만 심각한 증상은 아니었습니다.</koKR>
			<plPL>Strażnik Tirisfal to uosobienie dobra. Jakoś sobie radzi z demonicznym opętaniem.</plPL>
			<ptBR>O Guardião de Tirisfal é uma força do bem. A tal possessão demoníaca já está sob controle.</ptBR>
			<ruRU>Хранитель Тирисфаля — это сила, с которой стоит считаться. А одержимость демонами работе не мешает.</ruRU>
			<thTH>ผู้พิทักษ์แห่งทิริสฟอลคือพลังแห่งฝ่ายธรรมะ การมีปีศาจสิงร่างถือเป็นสภาวะที่ควบคุมได้</thTH>
			<zhCN>肩上担负的是守护提瑞斯法议会的重任，心中潜伏的是毁灭艾泽拉斯的恶魔。</zhCN>
			<zhTW>提里斯法守護者就是一股善的力量，就算有惡魔附身也不成問題。</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="HERODEF_ASSET_PATH">Assets/Game/GameObjects/HeroDefs/CollectionHeroDef_08a</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION" loc_ID="21121">
			<enUS>Guardian Medivh comes with an animated portrait, new visual effects, emotes and adds a new card back to your collection!\n\nMedivh uses your existing mage cards and the standard mage hero power.</enUS>
			<deDE>Der Wächter Medivh bietet ein animiertes Porträt, angepasste visuelle Effekte, neue Emotes und einen brandneuen Kartenrücken!\nMedivh kämpft mit Magierkarten und der Standard-Heldenfähigkeit des Magiers.</deDE>
			<esES>El guardián Medivh viene con un retrato animado, nuevos efectos visuales y frases, ¡y añade un nuevo dorso de carta a tu colección!\n\nMedivh utiliza tus cartas de mago y el poder de héroe de mago normal.</esES>
			<esMX>El Guardián Medivh viene con un retrato animado, nuevos efectos visuales y emociones. ¡Además agregará un dorso de carta a tu colección!\n\nMedivh usa las cartas de mago que ya tienes y el poder de héroe estándar de esa clase.</esMX>
			<frFR>Le gardien Medivh comprend un portrait animé, de nouveaux effets visuels, des emotes et un nouveau dos de carte pour votre collection !\n\nMedivh utilise les cartes mage déjà en votre possession et le pouvoir héroïque standard du mage.</frFR>
			<itIT>Il Guardiano Medivh si presenta con un ritratto animato, nuovi effetti visivi ed emote, e aggiunge un nuovo dorso alla tua collezione!\n\nMedivh usa il Potere Eroe e le carte in tuo possesso del Mago.</itIT>
			<jaJP>ガーディアンのメディヴには：動く肖像画、新たなエフェクト効果、メディヴならではの表現セリフ、そして新たなカード\n裏面デザインがついてきます！\n\nメディヴは既存のメイジ用のカードと、通常のメイジの\nヒーローパワーを使用します。</jaJP>
			<koKR>수호자 메디브 세트에는 움직이는 초상화, 새로운 시각 효과, 감정 표현, 그리고 카드 뒷면이 포함되어 있습니다!\n\n메디브는 내가 보유한 마법사 카드와 마법사의 기본 영웅 능력을 사용합니다.</koKR>
			<plPL>Strażnik Medivh dostępny jest wraz z animowanym portretem, nowymi efektami wizualnymi, emotkami oraz nowym rewersem kart.\n\nMedivh wykorzystuje istniejące karty maga oraz jego standardową moc specjalną.</plPL>
			<ptBR>O Guardião Medivh vem com um retrato animado, novos efeitos visuais, expressões e adiciona um novo verso de card à sua coleção!\n\nMedivh usa seus cards de mago existentes e o poder heroico de mago padrão.</ptBR>
			<ruRU>К этому герою прилагается анимированный портрет, новые графические эффекты, эмоции и новая рубашка для карт в вашей коллекции!\n\nМедив может использовать ваши карты мага и стандартную силу героя.</ruRU>
			<thTH>ผู้พิทักษ์เมดิฟห์มาพร้อมกับภาพประจำตัวขยับได้ รวมถึงวิชวลเอฟเฟกต์และการแสดงความรู้สึกแบบใหม่ และยังเพิ่มหลังการ์ดลายใหม่ให้คอลเลกชันของคุณด้วย!\n\nเมดิฟห์จะใช้การ์ดเมจของคุณ รวมถึงพลังฮีโร่มาตรฐานของเมจ</thTH>
			<zhCN>购买守护者麦迪文即可获得新的英雄头像、全新动画效果、表情以及一款新的卡牌背面图案！\n\n麦迪文将使用你现有的法师卡牌和英雄技能。</zhCN>
			<zhTW>守護者麥迪文擁有獨特的動態頭像，新的視覺效果和表情語音，並且還會增加一張全新的卡背到你的收藏！\n\n麥迪文可以沿用你擁有的法師卡牌和英雄能力。</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION_PHONE" loc_ID="22455">
			<enUS>Includes a new portrait, more visual effects &amp; emotes, and a card back!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Uses existing Mage cards and hero power.&lt;/color&gt;</enUS>
			<deDE>Umfasst ein neues Porträt, neue visuelle Effekte &amp; Emotes und einen Kartenrücken!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Verwendet schon bestehende Magierkarten und die gleiche Heldenfähigkeit.&lt;/color&gt;</deDE>
			<esES>¡Incluye un nuevo retrato, más efectos visuales y frases, y un dorso de carta!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Utiliza las cartas y el poder de héroe del mago.&lt;/color&gt;</esES>
			<esMX>Incluye un retrato nuevo, más efectos visuales y emociones, ¡y un dorso de carta!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Usa el poder de héroe y las cartas de Mago existentes.&lt;/color&gt;</esMX>
			<frFR>Comprend de nouveaux effets visuels, emotes, un portrait et un dos de carte !\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Utilise les cartes et le pouvoir héroïque de la classe mage.&lt;/color&gt;</frFR>
			<itIT>Include un nuovo ritratto, effetti visivi ed emote, e un dorso per le carte!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Usa il Potere Eroe e le carte della classe Mago.&lt;/color&gt;</itIT>
			<jaJP>新しい肖像画と視覚効果、専用の感情表現セリフと、新しいカード裏面デザインがついてくる！\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;既存のメイジ用のカードとヒーローパワーを使用。&lt;/color&gt;</jaJP>
			<koKR>새로운 초상화, 시각 효과, 감정 표현, 그리고 카드 뒷면이 포함되어 있습니다!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;내가 보유한 마법사 카드와 기본 영웅 능력을 사용합니다.&lt;/color&gt;</koKR>
			<plPL>Zawiera nowy portret, więcej efektów wizualnych\ni emotek, a także nowy rewers!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Wykorzystuje istniejące karty oraz moc specjalną maga.&lt;/color&gt;</plPL>
			<ptBR>Inclui um novo retrato, mais expressões e efeitos visuais e um verso de card!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Usa cards de Mago e poder heroico.&lt;/color&gt;</ptBR>
			<ruRU>Включает в себя новый портрет, расширенные графические эффекты и эмоции, а также рубашку для карт. \n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;Использует имеющиеся карты мага, а также стандартную силу героя. &lt;/color&gt;</ruRU>
			<thTH>มาพร้อมกับภาพประจำตัวใหม่ เพิ่มวิชวลเอฟเฟกต์และการแสดงความรู้สึก รวมถึงหลังการ์ด!\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;ใช้การ์ดและพลังฮีโร่ของเมจที่มีอยู่เดิม&lt;/color&gt;</thTH>
			<zhCN>购买即可获得新的英雄头像、全新动画效果、表情以及一款新的卡牌背面图案！\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;该英雄将使用你现有的法师卡牌和英雄技能。&lt;/color&gt;</zhCN>
			<zhTW>包括一套新的頭像，視覺效果，表情語音和卡背！\n&lt;color=#00000066&gt;沿用既有的法師卡牌和英雄能力。&lt;/color&gt;</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_BANNER_PREFAB" />
		<Field column="STORE_BACKGROUND_TEXTURE" />
		<Field column="STORE_SORT_ORDER">3</Field>
		<Field column="PURCHASE_COMPLETE_MSG" />
	</Record>
	<Record>
		<Field column="ID">13</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_ID">HERO_04a</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_BACK_ID" />
		<Field column="DESCRIPTION" loc_ID="21943">
			<enUS>Since the restoration of the Sunwell, the Blood Knight Matriarch's mood seems, well, sunnier!\n(Obtained by reaching level 20 on a new character in World of Warcraft.)</enUS>
			<deDE>Seit der Wiederherstellung des Sonnenbrunnens hat sich die Laune der Blutrittermatriarchin, sagen wir, aufgehellt!\n(Belohnung für alle Spieler, die in World of Warcraft mit einem neuen Charakter Stufe 20 erreichen.)</deDE>
			<esES>Desde la restauración de la Fuente del Sol, parece que la matriarca Caballero de sangre lo ve todo más... luminoso.\n(Se obtiene al subir al nivel 20 a un personaje nuevo en World of Warcraft).</esES>
			<esMX>Desde la restauración de la Fuente del Sol, el estado de ánimo de la Matriarca Caballero de sangre parece ser... ¡más radiante!\n(Obtenido por alcanzar el nivel 20 con un nuevo personaje en World of Warcraft)</esMX>
			<frFR>Depuis la restauration du Puits de soleil, la matriarche des chevaliers de sang a l’air d’humeur moins… sombre !\n(Obtenue en atteignant le niveau 20 avec un nouveau personnage dans World of Warcraft.)</frFR>
			<itIT>Da quando il Pozzo Solare è stato ripristinato, l'umore della Matriarca dei Cavalieri del Sangue è più... raggiante!\n(Ottenuto raggiungendo il livello 20 con un nuovo personaggio in World of Warcraft.)</itIT>
			<jaJP>太陽の泉が奪還されて以来、ブラッドナイトを統べる女傑も、まさに笑顔がサンサンと輝いているぞ！\n（「World of Warcraft」で新しいキャラクターをレベル20に到達してGET！）</jaJP>
			<koKR>태양샘이 정화된 후, 혈기사단의 지도자인 리아드린의 기분도 더욱 밝아졌습니다!\n(월드 오브 워크래프트에서 새로운 캐릭터로 20 레벨을 달성하여 획득)</koKR>
			<plPL>Od czasu odbudowy Słonecznej Studni nastrój Matrony Krwawych Elfów jest jakby bardziej... słoneczny!\nPortret przyznany za awans na 20 poziom nową postacią\nw World of Warcraft.</plPL>
			<ptBR>Desde a restauração da Nascente do Sol, o humor da Matriarca dos Cavaleiros Sangrentos parece, hum, mais ensolarado!\n\n(Adquirido ao chegar no nível 20 com um novo personagem em World of Warcraft.)</ptBR>
			<ruRU>После восстановления Солнечного Колодца настроение покровительницы рыцарей крови стало куда более... солнечным!\n\n(Награда за достижение 20-го уровня новым персонажем в World of Warcraft.)</ruRU>
			<thTH>ตั้งแต่ฟื้นฟูบ่อน้ำสุริยะได้สำเร็จ แม่ทัพหญิงแห่งบลัดไนท์ก็ดูสดใสขึ้นราวกับพระอาทิตย์ยามเช้า!\n(ได้รับจากการเล่นตัวละครใหม่จนถึงเลเวล 20 ใน World of Warcraft)</thTH>
			<zhCN>自从太阳之井被光复后，血骑士首领女伯爵莉亚德琳的心情也变得阳光了起来！\n在《魔兽世界》中将一名新角色升至20级获得该奖励。</zhCN>
			<zhTW>自從太陽之井恢復之後，血騎士團長的心情好像也變得更陽光了！\n(將《魔獸世界》角色升到第20級即可獲得。)</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="HERODEF_ASSET_PATH">Assets/Game/GameObjects/HeroDefs/CollectionHeroDef_04a</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION" />
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION_PHONE" />
		<Field column="STORE_BANNER_PREFAB" />
		<Field column="STORE_BACKGROUND_TEXTURE" />
		<Field column="STORE_SORT_ORDER" />
		<Field column="PURCHASE_COMPLETE_MSG" />
	</Record>
	<Record>
		<Field column="ID">14</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_ID">HERO_08b</Field>
		<Field column="CARD_BACK_ID" />
		<Field column="DESCRIPTION" loc_ID="22114">
			<enUS>His statue in Stormwind reflects his heroism, not his ego. Khadgar was available as a special promotion in April 2016.</enUS>
			<thTH>รูปปั้นของเขาในสตอร์มวินด์สื่อถึงความกล้าหาญของเขา ไม่เกี่ยวกับความหลงตัวเองเลยสักนิด รับคาดการ์ได้จากโปรโมชั่นพิเศษในเดือนเมษายน 2016 </thTH>
			<deDE>Die Größe seiner Statue in Sturmwind spiegelt seinen Heldenmut wider, nicht sein Ego. Khadgar war im Rahmen einer besonderen Aktion im April 2016 erhältlich.</deDE>
			<esES>Su estatua en Ventormenta refleja su heroísmo, no su ego. Khadgar estuvo disponible como promoción especial en abril de 2016.</esES>
			<esMX>Su estatua en Ventormenta es un reflejo de su heroísmo, no de su ego. Khadgar estaba disponible como promoción especial en abril de 2016.</esMX>
			<frFR>Sa statue à Hurlevent reflète son héroïsme, pas son ego. Khadgar était disponible pendant une promotion spéciale d’avril 2016.</frFR>
			<itIT>La sua statua a Roccavento ne celebra l'eroismo, non l'ego. Ottenuto attraverso una promozione speciale nell'aprile 2016.</itIT>
			<jaJP>ストームウィンドにある彼の像は、その勇壮たる魂を見事に描いているが、うぬぼれは表現しきれていない。カドガーは2016年4月のスペシャルプロモーションで入手可能だった。</jaJP>
			<koKR>스톰윈드에 세워진 카드가의 조각상에는 그의 영웅적인 기상이 잘 나타나 있습니다. 근거 없는 자부심이 아니라고요. 카드가는 2016년 4월에 진행되는 특별 프로모션에 참여하여 획득할 수 있습니다.</koKR>
			<plPL>Jego posąg w Wichrogrodzie ukazuje heroizm, a nie ego. Khadgar był dostępny w specjalnej promocji w kwietniu 2016.</plPL>
			<ptBR>A estátua dele em Ventobravo reflete o seu heroísmo, não seu ego. Hadggar foi disponibilizado numa promoção especial em abril de 2016.</ptBR>
			<ruRU>Его статуя в Штормграде символизирует героизм, а не самовлюбленность. Кадгар был доступен в рамках специальной акции в апреле 2016 г.</ruRU>
			<zhCN>卡德加的雕像矗立在暴风城中，他的英勇事迹将永远被铭记。\n你可以在2016年4月的一个特殊的推广活动中购买卡德加。</zhCN>
			<zhTW>暴風城門口的雕像要紀念的是他的英雄氣概，而不是他超冷的派對笑話。你可以在2016年4月的促銷活動中購買卡德加。</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="HERODEF_ASSET_PATH">Assets/Game/GameObjects/HeroDefs/CollectionHeroDef_08b</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION" loc_ID="22371">
			<enUS>Khadgar comes with an animated portrait, new visual effects and emotes, uses your existing mage cards and standard mage hero power.</enUS>
			<deDE>Khadgar bietet ein animiertes Porträt sowie neue visuelle Effekte und Emotes! Er kämpft mit den Karten und der Standard-Heldenfähigkeit des Magiers.</deDE>
			<esES>Khadgar viene con un retrato animado, nuevos efectos visuales y frases, utiliza las cartas de mago existentes y el poder de héroe estándar del mago.</esES>
			<esMX>Khadgar viene con un retrato animado, nuevos efectos visuales y emociones; usa las cartas de mago que ya tienes y el poder de héroe estándar de los magos.</esMX>
			<frFR>Khadgar bénéficie d’un portrait animé et de nouveaux effets visuels et emotes. Il utilise les cartes et le pouvoir héroïque de la classe mage.</frFR>
			<itIT>Khadgar si presenta con un ritratto animato, nuovi effetti visivi ed emote, e usa il Potere Eroe e le carte in tuo possesso del Mago.</itIT>
			<jaJP>カドガーには、アニメーションする肖像画と新しい視覚効果、専用の感情表現セリフがついてくる。既存のメイジ用のカードと、通常のメイジのヒーローパワーを使用する。</jaJP>
			<koKR>카드가 세트에는 움직이는 초상화, 새로운 시각 효과, 감정 표현이 포함되어 있습니다. 카드가는 내가 보유한 마법사 카드와 마법사의 기본 영웅 능력을 사용합니다.</koKR>
			<plPL>Khadgar dostępny jest wraz z animowanym portretem, nowymi efektami wizualnymi i emotkami. Wykorzystuje istniejące karty oraz moc specjalną maga.</plPL>
			<ptBR>Hadggar vem com um retrato animado, novos efeitos visuais e expressões. Ele usa os cards de mago que você já tem e o poder heroico de mago padrão. </ptBR>
			<ruRU>К этому герою прилагается анимированный портрет, новые графические эффекты и эмоции. Кадгар использует имеющиеся карты мага, а также стандартную силу героя. </ruRU>
			<thTH>คาดการ์มาพร้อมกับภาพประจำตัวขยับได้ รวมถึงวิชวลเอฟเฟกต์และการแสดงความรู้สึกแบบใหม่ โดยจะใช้การ์ดเมจของคุณ รวมถึงพลังฮีโร่มาตรฐานของเมจ</thTH>
			<zhCN>购买大法师卡德加即可获得新的英雄头像、全新动画效果及表情，卡德加将使用你现有的法师卡牌和英雄技能。</zhCN>
			<zhTW>卡德加擁有獨特的動態頭像，新的視覺效果和表情語音。他可以沿用你擁有的法師卡牌和英雄能力。</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_DESCRIPTION_PHONE" loc_ID="22456">
			<enUS>Includes a new portrait, more visual effects &amp; emotes! Uses existing mage cards and hero power.</enUS>
			<deDE>Umfasst ein neues Porträt, angepasste visuelle Effekte &amp; neue Emotes! Verwendet Magierkarten und die gleiche Heldenfähigkeit.</deDE>
			<esES>¡Incluye un nuevo retrato, más efectos visuales y frases! Utiliza las cartas y el poder de héroe del mago.</esES>
			<esMX>¡Incluye un retrato nuevo, más efectos visuales y emociones! Usa el poder de héroe y las cartas de Mago existentes.</esMX>
			<frFR>Comprend un portrait et de nouveaux effets visuels et emotes ! Utilise les cartes et le pouvoir héroïque de la classe mage.</frFR>
			<itIT>Include un nuovo ritratto, effetti visivi ed emote. Usa il Potere Eroe e le carte della classe Mago.</itIT>
			<jaJP>新しい肖像画と視覚効果、専用の感情表現セリフがついてくる！既存のメイジ用のカードとヒーローパワーを使用する。</jaJP>
			<koKR>새로운 초상화, 시각 효과, 감정 표현이 포함되어 있습니다! 내가 보유한 마법사 카드와 기본 영웅 능력을 사용합니다.</koKR>
			<plPL>Zawiera nowy portret, więcej efektów wizualnych i emotek! Wykorzystuje istniejące karty oraz moc specjalną maga.</plPL>
			<ptBR>Inclui um novo retrato, mais expressões e efeitos visuais! Usa o poder heroico e os cards de mago que você já tem.</ptBR>
			<ruRU>Включает в себя новый портрет, расширенные графические эффекты и эмоции, использует имеющиеся карты мага, а также стандартную силу героя. </ruRU>
			<thTH>มาพร้อมกับภาพประจำตัวใหม่ เพิ่มวิชวลเอฟเฟกต์และการแสดงความรู้สึก! ใช้การ์ดและพลังฮีโร่ของเมจที่มีอยู่เดิม</thTH>
			<zhCN>购买即可获得新的英雄头像、全新动画效果及表情，将使用你现有的法师卡牌和英雄技能。</zhCN>
			<zhTW>包括一套新的頭像，視覺效果和表情語音！沿用既有的法師卡牌和英雄能力。</zhTW>
		</Field>
		<Field column="STORE_BANNER_PREFAB" />
		<Field column="STORE_BACKGROUND_TEXTURE" />
		<Field column="STORE_SORT_ORDER">0</Field>
		<Field column="PURCHASE_COMPLETE_MSG" />
	</Record>
</Dbf>